softmoc.com 2015-05-29

# SoftMoc Privacy Statement | SoftMoc.com

SoftMoc Inc. & SoftMoc.com are constantly striving to provide excellent service to you, our customers, while building a long-lasting relationship. To achieve these goals, we occasionally need information about you when you visit our site. 

SoftMoc Inc. & SoftMoc.com respects your right to privacy. When you visit SoftMoc.com, you may be providing information to us on two different levels about your visit: 

  * Anonymous statistics collected as you browse the site
  * Personal information you knowingly give us. 

We want you to be aware of how we handle this information.

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

SoftMoc Inc. & SoftMoc.com would like to assure you that **WE DO NOT** : 

  * Collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. 
  * Provide or sell the names and addresses of our customers [site users] to outside vendors. 

SoftMoc Inc. & SoftMoc.com does: 

  * Safeguard customers' information from unauthorized access. 
  * Collect, maintain and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customers' needs (e.g. customer care or new products or services). 
  * Honor customers' requests to remove their names from our e-mail solicitation lists.
  * Maintain confidentiality of customer information when undertaking projects with other companies. 

SoftMoc Inc. & SoftMoc.com values your privacy, and we reinforce this belief throughout our organization. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific web page says otherwise. 

### Statistics about your visit

As you browse the site, SoftMoc.com web servers and select 3rd party analytics providers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via web server logs, we monitor statistics such as:

  * How many people visit our site
  * Which pages people visit on our site
  * From which domains our visitors come (e.g., "mindspring.net" or "aol.com")
  * Which browsers people use to visit our site 

While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our Web site, to monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use.

Ad networks, including Google, may show you ads on sites on the internet based on your browser cookies and your visit history on our website. These ads are based on your anonymous browsing patterns & interests, not your personally identifiable information. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

#### Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

Your personal information you submit is never shared with any third parties unless it is necessary to complete your request.
